WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
I'd like to prove that
I could become a splendid Ninja
even though I can't
use Ninjutsu or Genjutsu!
That would be the ultimate for me!
All right!
I'm going to do my best again today!
Oh! Bushy Brow!
Oh... Good morning, Naruto-kun.
Hey, hey, did you already get checked out
by Granny Tsunade?
How was it, how was it?
The Leaf Village is
in great trouble right now,
so we must do our best!
You're right.
Bushy Brow, you should get better
as soon as possible
and succeed in your mis...!
— Naruto nii-chan!
What's the matter?
It's Konohamaru-chan!
Huh? What's wrong with Konohamaru?
He's in trouble.
In trouble?!
The One Who Succeeds
The Will of Fire
At this rate,
we will have to open it by force.
Try it! Who do you think I am?!
I am the grandson of
the Third Hokage!
If you go against me, then...
Old man...
It means you're going
against the Hokage!
We need Tsunade-sama
to assume her position immediately.
Those are Pepper Smoke Bombs!
You'll get something even more terrible
if you come close to me.
Honorable Grandson! Even for you...
There are things that can
and cannot be forgiven!
Shut up!
What is all this commotion
so early in the morning?
It's hurting my head.
Tsunade-sama...
It's just one kid...
What're you doing?
Yes...
Get rid of him!
But it's the grandson
of the Third Hokage!
It doesn't matter if
he's the grandson or the great grandson.
I am the granddaughter
of the First Hokage!
He might just open his eyes
if he gets roughed up a little.
Now move it!
— Yes!
Wait!
Naruto-kun?!
Hey, hold on there.
I don't really know
what's going on,
but don't be so rough with Konohamaru,
Granny Tsunade.
An acquaintance of yours?
Yes, yes...
I'll do the convincing,
leave it to me.
Then, do something
by the end of the day!
Oh, Tsunade-sama... Please wait!
Excuse me.
Oh, Sakura-chan. Sasuke-kun has already
been discharged from the hospital.
I'm actually here to see Lee-san today.
Is he in the rehabilitation room?
Not yet.
That's not like him to be late.
I see.
The probability of a successful surgery
is 50%, at best.
And if it fails, you'll die!
Hey, Konohamaru.
What are you doing in there?!
Hurry up and come out.
Then let's go eat some ramen.
Don't worry. It's on me!
You can have lots of BBQ pork, too!
All right! You can have eggs too!
How about that!
At least answer me!
Shut up, you fool!
You called me a fool!
Open up already! I'll break in! Hey!
Try if you can!
W-Why you...!
— Naruto nii-chan...
— Naruto nii-chan!
Oh, Lee-san... You're here.
S-Sakura-san!
I wanted to bring you this.
F-For... me?
Th-Thank you very much!
I-I'm sorry, Sakura-san.
No worries.
Sasuke-kun is now recuperating at home.
Thanks to Tsunade-sama.
At this rate,
seems like he'll be able
to get back to his duties very soon.
I see. That's very good.
Tsunade-sama is great, after all.
I think if you had her take a look,
you'd get better very quickly.
Yes...
But if there is something
that I can do,
please feel free to tell me.
Thank you very much, Sakura-san.
Then I'll see you soon.
I would think that at least
one bar would be open.
There's no way.
What time do you think it is right now?
I can't drink alcohol, and I can't gamble.
This place, the Hidden Leaf Village,
is no fun at all.
Just like the Third Hokage.
Tsunade-sama!
Oh, I'm tired.
I just want to sit down and
have a drink somewhere.
I understand.
I will take you to a place where
you can sit and have a drink.
What?
But I will have you do your work!
Here now, go ahead. It's hot.
Shizune... you've suddenly
become very strict!
I haven't gotten strict.
It's probably that you were not aware.
Not aware?!
"If I can't get in the room,
then I don't have to work."
Isn't that what you were thinking?
And that's why
you left it up to Naruto-kun.
Humph! Could be...
This is the most recent list
of Shinobi.
The names and lineups of
the groups have changed a lot.
So please look through them.
And I mean, look through all of it!
Oh, boy.
They have sweet rice cakes, too.
I don't like sweet things!
Hey! Konohamaru, come out already!
At least tell me why you're doing this!
Konohamaru-chan!
Damn!
Everybody came here because
they're worried about you!
If you don't come out,
I'm going to drag you out of there!
Naruto Sacred Technique...
Sexy Jutsu!
Konohamaru-kun, come out!
Konohamaru-kun, hurry!
Hey! Say something at least!
This is so embarrassing!
Don't fool around with me!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
— Stop it already, Konohamaru!
One, two...
— Uh, what is this?
— What the...?!
What's going on?!
Are you okay? Naruto nii-chan?
This is the Grandpa's room.
Eight D-rank missions,
three C-rank missions...
I see, very much like the Kurenai team.
We can easily figure out
what the Third Hokage was thinking.
This is the same as
their parents' team.
I see.
Oh, I see. This team has their own specialty
and is well-balanced.
My shoulders are stiff.
I'm going to go get
some fresh air outside.
Success...
Naruto nii-chan...
Uh... damn!
If that's how you're going to be,
then I'm not going to go easy on you.
This is Grandpa's room!
I won't let anybody
use this room besides him!
Grandpa's...?
That's why, as his grandson,
I'm going to protect it!
Fool! This isn't the time for that!
The Leaf Village is in great danger!
So what?! It doesn't matter to me.
Are you seriously saying that?!
Oh, now I'm mad!
And I can easily tear down one
or two doors with my new powers...!
— Naruto nii-chan!
Granny Tsunade...
Oh! Watch out!
W-Wow...
Listen Konohamaru.
The Hidden Leaf Village is
in great trouble right now!
Our forces have dropped to almost half,
and we have to finish our missions!
That's what I taught you!
Yeah... um... well...
But if we don't accomplish
our missions,
that's letting other countries know
that the village has been weakened.
That's what Iruka-sensei taught you!
Do you not like Granny Tsunade?
It's not that!
It's not that at all.
Then what is it?
Soon, nobody will call me
Honorable Grandson.
Then I'll just become
plain old Konohamaru.
So what's wrong with
plain old Konohamaru?
No...
Why, why?! You hated
being called Honorable Grandson!
Everybody's going to forget
about Grandpa.
Grandpa.
They're going to forget what
a great Ninja he was,
they're just going to put him away
like an old ashtray.
The new Hokage will make all kinds
of changes in the Leaf Village.
That's not true!
The Hidden Leaf Village is
the Hidden Leaf Village.
And besides,
nobody will forget about the Old Man!
No! They will never forget about him!
They will forget, I guarantee it.
They won't forget!
That's a lie!
It's not a lie!
You can't believe what I am saying?!
That's right, I can't!
Oh boy!
Come with me, Konohamaru!
We just have to get Granny Tsunade
to promise
that she won't change
the Village Hidden in the Leaves.
And then on top of that,
we can get everybody to promise us
that they won't forget about the Old Man!
What?
Isn't that what you want?
I can't believe that I let
Tsunade-sama out of my sight!
Did you find her, Tonton?
Revitalizing the cells, I see.
I've found you Tsunade-sama.
What?
Tsunade-sama is studying?!
Be quiet! I can't concentrate.
Concentrate?!
I've never heard you use that word
except when you're gambling.
Is that Shizune nee-chan's voice?
Shizune...
Do you remember that Medical Ninja
by the name of Kabuto?
What about him?
His ability to create new cells.
I was researching ways to use
that power on the patients.
For Lee-kun?
If the 50% chance becomes 51%,
it's worth a try.
It really depends on the individual's
traits.
Even for you,
it might be hard to acquire those powers.
I'll just have to try.
I am the Fifth Hokage, after all.
It can't be helped, Konohamaru.
I am the Third Hokage, after all.
If you don't like it,
you should just quit!
Everybody from the village
is my family.
To protect the family,
that is the duty of a Hokage.
Oh! Grandpa!
Just for today,
I'm making a special exception.
What's the matter Konohamaru?
Don't you want to see
Grannny Tsunade?
No.
I'll just have to do it.
I am the Fifth Hokage, after all.
It can't be helped, Konohamaru.
I am the Third Hokage, after all.
It can't be helped.
I am the Honorable Grandson, after all.
Huh?
I am Konohamaru of
the Hidden Leaf Village, after all!
H-Hey Konohamaru, wait!
What's going on with him?
Hey, Konohamaru!
Tsunade-sama?
Nothing...
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
Back then, Sensei taught me
that I would grow up to become
a great Ninja
through lots of effort and
competition with my rivals.
His words put me at ease.
A path opened up for me
just when I was unsure of myself.
I realized that all I had to do
was try my best.
But now...
Next time:
"The Bond Between the Hot-Blooded Teacher and Pupil. When a Man Follows His Ninja Way."